not only doesn't tell a guy idea
不仅不告诉男主意
providing sting completion on a key by
通过提供密钥完成敲击
key basis it also offers something
关键基础还提供了一些东西
called smart completion which offers
称为智能补全
context-sensitive completion results
上下文相关的完成结果
with full type matching so that the type
具有完整的类型匹配，因此类型
you expect is the type that comes first
您期望的是最先出现的类型
and you've seen how some of that works
您已经了解了其中的一些工作原理
already with basic completion and type
已经基本完成并输入了类型
aware completion but that's only one
有意识的完成，但这仅仅是一个
part of intelligent code completion
智能代码完成的一部分
IntelliJ IDEA so in areas where IntelliJ
IntelliJ IDEA在IntelliJ的地区也是如此
IDEA knows that type is constrained
IDEA知道类型受到限制
you'll be able to use that built-in type
您将能够使用该内置类型
inference to narrow down the completion
推断范围缩小
results and this is done automatically
结果，这是自动完成的
so for example here if the object that
因此，例如，如果对象
we receive is an instance of long when
我们收到的是long当
we do something like try to increment
我们做类似尝试增加
the counter an apply smart completion
柜台申请智能完成
then it will automatically cast that
然后它将自动投射
variable down to a long and similarly if
变小到很长，如果
it's an integer then it will offer the
这是一个整数，那么它将提供
same feature so this happens
同样的功能，所以会发生这种情况
automatically and it's powered by
自动并且由
something called dataflow analysis so in
所谓的数据流分析
any symbol inside the IDE you can right
您可以在IDE中找到任何符号
click on that symbol and analyze the
单击该符号并分析
data flow to and from that location
往返该位置的数据流
throughout your entire project that will
在整个项目中
display a hierarchy of all the places
显示所有地点的层次结构
that object has been upstream and how I
那物体一直在上游，我如何
travel to that location in your code
前往代码中的该位置
using that information in the enclosing
在附件中使用该信息
type IntelliJ IDEA is able to determine
IntelliJ IDEA类型可以确定
the most specific data type that an
最具体的数据类型
object could possibly hold at any given
对象可能在任何给定位置都可以容纳
location another area where smart
放置另一个聪明的地方
completion is really helpful is in
完成真的很有帮助
constructors and methods which pass
通过的构造函数和方法
their arguments directly into another
他们的论点直接进入另一个
method so here IntelliJ IDEA uses type
方法，因此此处IntelliJ IDEA使用类型
inference and variable names determine
推论和变量名决定
which argument should be placed in which
哪个参数应该放在哪个
position completion is also available in
位置完成功能也可以在
other areas where your program's
您程序所在的其他区域
functionality may span different
功能可能会有所不同
languages and build tools which may have
语言和构建工具可能
cross language references here you'll be
跨语言参考，您将在这里
able to use completion just like in your
能够像您一样使用完成功能
native programming language
本机编程语言
this is also available in embedded
这也可以在嵌入式中使用
languages and dialects as well so for
语言和方言
writing a sequel query inside Java for
在Java中编写续集查询
instance we can use completion for
实例，我们可以使用完成
syntactical elements as well as real
句法要素以及真实要素
data sources inside a database
数据库内部的数据源
notice that when you use completion you
请注意，当您使用完成功能时，
can use any substring of the symbol that
可以使用该符号的任何子字符串
you'd like to complete or hippy
你想完成或嬉皮
completion by just using the first
只需使用第一个即可完成
letters of the camel cased words finally
骆驼的信件终于把单词
you can configure the behavior of code
您可以配置代码的行为
completion inside your settings which
在您的设置内完成
will allow you to customize
将允许您自定义
case-sensitive completion Auto inserting
区分大小写的完成自动插入
lexicographic order and the code
词典顺序和代码
completion and documentation pop-ups
完成和文档弹出窗口
with a default delay set to a second and
默认延迟设置为1秒，
toggle the full signatures of each of
切换每个的完整签名
the methods
方法